We're going to do a nice little peck stretch for Keri here.
So I'm going to come up, first starting in kneeling diamond.
I'm going to place a pillow on her back, and that's the reason is, is I'm going to be putting my knee into her back and I don't want to crunch bones against bones.
We want make sure they're comfortable.
And also you're safe.
So first placing my knee into her back.
Now I'm in a nice warrior stance.
I'm going to slightly slide my opposite leg back so I have some nice steadiness there.
I'm going to sweep down, grab a hold of this hand place it behind the head.
Sweep down, bring it back.
And ask your client to intertwine their fingers.
Now slightly have them lean back just a few inches.
Take your hands on the outside and just gently start opening up.
Talk to your client.
Let them know is that enough?
Too much?
Little more.
Little more?
Good.
Now ease off, and then do it again.
Open up, good peck stretch here.
One more time.
Easing off.
And gently opening it up.
Perfect.
Ease them up slowly.
Sweep the arms down, have a hand on your shoulders, steady yourself as you come down.